[On Xu Qingdao's birthday]
Tianbai,
do you think I should go?
Of course.
This meal is your best chance,
and also
your last chance.
Let's go.
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 21]
Who is it?
Miss,
why are you here?
Are you going to attack me?
No.
Miss, what are you talking about?
Hurry up and leave.
You're an eyesore here.
I'm leaving.
Come out.
The key to Xu Qingdao's safe.
Don't look around after you go in.
It will make him suspicious.
Yes.
Blue.
It seems this is the antidote.
After waiting for so long,
the distinguished guest
has finally arrived.
You must be joking, Sir.
Don't be so polite.
After all, we're so close.
Tianbai,
we meet again.
You're surprised, aren't you?
Director.
It doesn't matter what you call me.
What's important is that
the person is right,
then everything is right.
Chief Xu, don't you agree?
You are right.
Come on,
what are you waiting for?
Have a seat.
Sir used the lives of 58 dock workers
from the Qingtian Gang
to threaten Lu Wenbiao.
If he transports the goods just once,
and he would let them go.
Lu Wenbiao agreed.
What an idiot.
Sir works for foreigners,
conducting Wolfbane experiments
in Ningcheng.
Sir said they are all consumables.
The more people die,
the more data we get.
Some of my subordinates
were also involved in the experiment.
They have good foundations,
so they are used to study
the maintenance dose.
Their lives are worthless anyway.
Chief Xu,
you've worked hard all these years.
Come,
let me toast you.
Not at all.
The Shisha Gang owes its success today
to you.
I'll drink it all, you can drink
as you please.
Do you really think so?
Of course.
We are all old.
Ningcheng ultimately belongs to
the young people.
Chief Xu,
today is your birthday.
I specially prepared a gift for you.
Great.
This is...
This is to make you keep your eyes open
and see the people around you clearly.
Otherwise, you wouldn't even know
if an undercover infiltrated Shisha Gang.
What?
You are the birthday boy today,
so I won't let you do it.
I'll do it.
So it's him.
Lu Ye.
Something’s wrong.
Something happened at Dashijie.
Are you shocked?
Don't be afraid.
You know I'm the real undercover.
Why?
It doesn't matter who you are.
What matters is that you are useful.
And he is useless.
Useless things should be thrown away.
You've been undercover by his side
for so long,
and he didn't even notice.
What's the point of keeping
a piece of trash like him?
Why would I give you up for him?
You've always been
my favorite subordinate.
Come.
Sit.
I suppose
you still have many questions for me.
Go ahead.
The mole in the police station
is your man.
That's why we couldn't find anything
no matter how hard we tried.
Don't put it so harshly.
They are your colleagues
and my subordinates.
Everyone just does their own job
and manages different areas.
You colluded with the gang
and even split the police station
into two factions.
Your people have long become corrupt cops.
Smart.
From the very beginning,
you knew about my undercover plan
with Master.
All of this
was tacitly approved by you.
That's right.
Why didn't you stop it?
Why should I?
With you there,
you could keep an eye on things for me.
Xu Qingdao has never been honest.
And I also wanted to see your abilities
and how far you could go.
Sure enough,
you didn't let me down.
What exactly do you want to do?
I want
to give the Shisha Gang to you.
Don't rush.
I know what you want to say.
Officer Shen is the embodiment of justice.
Why would he be willing to do
such a thing?
But let me tell you,
what I can give you
is far more than you can imagine.
Wealth,
power,
and fame.
When you have all of this,
any of them
is much more interesting
than your so-called justice.
Even if
you are not interested in this,
don't you
want to protect Ningcheng?
Tianbai.
I think you also know
that the line between black and white
is hard to distinguish.
To control the darkness,
the best way is to blend into it.
Once you become the leader of Shisha Gang,
I promise
you will be in charge of the underworld.
How about it?
Are you tempted?
Will you agree?
I won't agree.
Who is it?
Stop.
I've always wanted to know
who exactly is helping the Qingtian Gang
make a comeback.
So it's you, Sir.
You're quite a clever kid.
You flatter me.
But not clever enough to read your mind.
You promised to support our Qingtian Gang.
Why did you go back on your word?
Xu Qingdao is dead.
Perfect.
The Shisha Gang has disbanded.
So his territory should be mine.
What do you mean by letting him take over?
Enough.
Stop acting.
Did you think I didn't know
about your little tricks?
But I am quite curious.
Why are you working
with your father's murderer?
Because I know you are the real murderer.
You used the lives
of our Qingtian Gang brothers
to blackmail my father
into smuggling drugs for you.
Then you exposed it
and silenced him.
What a great scheme.
Not bad.
Very impressive.
I didn't think you would find out
about this.
You two young men are indeed outstanding.
In that case,
let me add one more detail.
Actually, in the very beginning,
I had my eyes on your father,
not Xu Qingdao.
I tried to persuade him nicely,
but your father just wouldn't agree.
He even said he hated drugs the most
in his life.
Since that was the case,
I made sure he died from drugs,
in infamy,
and despised by everyone.
Do you think
you can see through everything
and control everyone?
Then guess
why I'm sitting here wasting my breath
on you.
What?
Young Master.